你是谁
who are you?
卡西迪奥
castiello.
我是侍奉主的天使
i'm an angel of the lord.
安娜
anna?
你知道你在哪儿吗
do you know where you are?
知道你为什么在这儿吗
do you know why you here?
还记得你做过什么吗
do you remember what you did?
我
i...
我想设法警告他们
i was trying to warn them.
警告谁
warn who?
每一个人
everyone.
忘了吧
forget it.
这听来了很傻
it was stupid.
你想警告他们的是什么
what were you trying to warn them about?
听着
look...
我知道的
i get it.
你认为我是疯了
you think i'm nuts.
如果我是你  我也会认为我疯了
if i were you,i'd think i was nuts.
但我所说的都是真的
but it's all true.
没关系的  你可以告诉我
it's okay. you can tell me.
我洗耳恭听
i'm here to listen.
世界末日
the end...
就要来了
is coming.
天启
the apocalypse.
是圣经里所讲的
like in the bible?
差不多
kind of.
我的意思是  最终的结果都是一样
i mean,same bottom line.
有一个恶魔  叫莉莉丝的
this demon,lilith,
想要打破66个封印
is trying to break the 66 seals
解放被禁锢在地狱的路西法
to free lucifer from hell.
路西法
lucifer...
将会带着天启降临
will bring the apocalypse.
所以
so...
如果抓住它们就得马上干掉
smoke 'em if you got 'em.
安娜
anna?
对不起
sorry.
你刚刚在干嘛
what were you doing?
没什么
nothing.
只是在聆听
just listening.
那么  你刚才所说的
so,you were saying
在这个世界上有66个封印
that there are,uh,66 of these seals in the world?
不  不对
no. no.
是有差不多6000个封印
there are about 6,000 possible seals,
而莉莉丝只是要破坏其中的66个
and lilith only has to break 66 of them,
而且没有人知道她是要破坏哪66个封印
and no one knows which 66 she's gonna break.
我明白了
i see.
这就是无法阻止她的原因
that's why it's nearly impossible to stop her.
也是天使会失败的原因
and that's why the angels are losing.
这就是我们为什么都要灭亡的原因
that's why we're all gonna die.
本德医生请到神经科
dr. bender to the mental ward,please.
本德医生
dr. bender.
服药时间到了  安娜
time for your meds,anna.
安娜
anna
怎么呢  美女
what's the matter,sweetie?
你的脸  你的脸怎么了
your face --what happened to your face?!
我知道
i know.
我帅到让你想亲我了
i'm downright kissable.
布莱恩  拜托  伙计  再来一次就好
brian,come on,man,just one more.
至  至少给我一次反败为胜的机会
just -- just give me a chance to win it back.
反正是你的钱
it's your cash.
打扰下
excuse me.
我弟弟有点喝醉了
my brother's a little sauced to be making bets.
嘿  他自己要的
hey. he insisted.
是的  钱你已经到手了
yeah,but you've already taken,
怎么  你想再洗劫他一次
what,two bills off him?
我刚刚说过了
i'm just saying.
嘿  收声  迪恩  我很清醒
hey,shut up,dean.i'm fine.
不  你一点都不清醒  你醉了
no,you're not fine.you're drunk!
我们赌500元
let's make it $500.
500元
$500?
没问题
sure.
500元
$500.
你来开局
your break.
看着钱
keep the money.
keep the money?
什么意思
what --
不错  你可真是无处不在啊
well,you got a lot of nerve showing up anywhere near me.
我只是来告诉你们一些信息  说完我就离开
i just have some info and then i'm gone.
是什么
what is it?
我收到一些小道消息
i'm hearing a few whispers.
哦  真好  恶魔的小道消息  那一定很可靠
ooh,great,demon whisperers --that's reliable.
一个叫安娜·米尔顿的姑娘
girl named anna milton
昨晚从一个反锁的房间逃走了
escaped from a locked ward yesterday.
恶魔们都十分积极地想要找到她
the demons seem pretty keen on finding her.
似乎  还有些重要人物都现身了
apparently,some real heavy hitters turned out
就为了追捕这个复活节彩蛋[指安娜]
for the easter-egg hunt.
-为什么  她是什么人物  -不清楚
-why? who is she? - No idea.
但我认为她一定很重要
but i'm thinking that she's important,
因为追捕的要求是她得是活的
'cause the order is to capture her alive.
我觉得不管这个交易是怎么回事
i just figured that whatever the deal is,
你必须在恶魔之前找到她
you might want to find this girl before the demons do.
听着  也许我们应该去查一查
look,maybe we should check it out.
-事实上  我们已经有案子在查了  不过还是谢谢你  -什么案子
-actually,we're working a case,but thanks.-what case?
-嗯  我们已经有头绪了  很大的突破  -听来了真是恐怖啊
-uh,we've got leads,big leads.-sounds dangerous.
是的  追着几个婊子可不会让我们徒劳无获
yeah,well,it sure ain't goosechasing after some chick
谁来着  据我们了解  那根本就不存在
who,for all we know,doesn't even exist,
仅仅就因为你说她很重要
just because you say she's important.
我只是来告诉你们这个消息的
i'm just delivering the news.
你们要怎么做是你们的事
you can do whatever you want with it.
就我而言  我已经告诉你们了  我的任务就完成了
far as i'm concerned,i told you,i'm done.
等等  等等  安娜逃出来的那家医院
wait,wait,wait. this hospital anna escaped from --
叫啥名字
it got a name?
我能拿一份失踪人口报告吗
can i get a copy of the missing-persons report?
太好了  好吧  谢谢
great. okay. thanks.
安娜·米尔顿是真有其人
well,anna milton's definitely real.
并不意味着这件案件也是真的
don't mean the case is real.
去那家医院要三日车程
and this hospital's a three-day drive.
我们也差不多到了  迪恩
we've driven further for less,dean.
你有话就说  尽管说
you got something to say,say it.
我想说  真他妈的
oh,i'm saying it -- this sucks.
你不气吗  我们在追那女孩
you're not pissed we're going after the girl.
-你很气  露比让我们走这趟  -是的
-you're pissed ruby threw us the tip. -right.
正因为你相当关心她
'cause as far as you're concerned,
事实上地狱里的婊子都是一伙的
the hell-bitch is practically family.
是的 伙计  有些事情是注定要发生的
yeah,boy,something major must've happened
当我从地狱回来站在阳光普照的大地上时
while i downstairs,'cause i come back,
你不正和
and -- and you're bff with a demon?
我告诉你了  迪恩  她来帮我追杀莉莉丝的
i told you,dean,she helped me go after lilith.
谢谢你的描述  非常生动
well,thanks for the thumbnail -- real vivid.
你想要更多细节吗
you want to fill in a little detail?
当然  迪恩  我们轮流说
sure,dean,let's trade stories.
你先说  到底怎么了  别漏了细节
you first. how was hell? don't spare the details.
出现吧
come on!
你到底在哪
where the hell are you?!
我还在想你会不会来
i was wondering whether to come or not.
我是说  你杀了我的帮手
i mean,you shot one of my co-workers.
别冲动  萨姆
don't take this the wrong way,sam,
你不是个容易冲动的人  伙计
but you don't look so hot,buddy.
我猜你并不想烧了你哥哥的尸体
i guess burying your brother didn't agree with you.
那么
well...
让我先看看你的特制匕首吧
well,let's see that special little knife of yours first.
我们都没武器了
no devil's traps,either.
我到这里不是来玩的
i'm not here to play games.
让我猜猜
well,let me guess.
想做个交易
you want to make a deal.
放温彻斯特父子离开
and 'round and 'round the winchesters go.
对不起  萨姆  我不会答应的
i'm sorry,sam. that's not gonna happen.
我不想再活十年了
i don't want 10 years.
一年也不要
i don't want one year.
我什么都不想要
i don't want candy!
我只想和迪恩换个地方
i want to trade places with dean.
不行
no.
带我走  这很公平
just take me! it's a fair trade!
不行
no!
为什么不
why not?
莉莉丝要让我死
lilith wants me dead.
那就让迪恩走  我来成全她
just let dean go,and she can have me.
你还不明白吗  萨姆  这和你的灵魂无关
don't you understand,sam? it's not about your soul.
迪恩在地狱里  这正是我们想要的
dean's in hell,right where we want him.
我们一切想要的什么都得到了
we've got everything exactly the way we want it.
你想杀了我吗  杀吧
you want to kill me?! go ahead.
我的主人什么都安排好了
i've made peace with my lord.
现在他对安娜逃走的事一点都想不起来吗
now,the orderly has no recollection of anna's escape?
很显然  他被她打晕了
apparently,she knocked him unconscious.
引发了健忘症
the blow caused some amnesia.
他甚至连走进她房间都忘了
he doesn't even remember coming into her room.
下得真他妈的重手
that's a hell of a right hook
她击倒了一个比她重80磅的家伙
to knock out a guy that's got 80 pounds on her.
我想她是算好了的
we think she may have planned this,
-在外面等着吧  -好的
-waited behind the door. -right.
你提到过安娜的病是最近才有的
uh,you mentioned anna's illness was recent.
两个月前  她还好好的
two months ago,she was happy,
精神很好  从事新闻业
well-adjusted,journalism major,
朋友很多  前途无量
lots of friends -- bright future.
发生什么了  疯了吗
so,what happened -- she just...flipped?
那是精神分裂症引起的悲剧
well,that's the tragedy of schizophrenia.
几星期之内  安娜因错觉而精神崩溃
within weeks,anna was overtaken by delusions.
什么样的错觉
what kind of delusions?
我认为恶魔无处不在
she thought demons were everywhere.
真有趣
huh. interesting.
对我们的病人来说并不寻常
it's not uncommon for our patients
会相信恶魔是存在的
to believe that monsters are real.
那  那可真古怪
well,that -- that's just batty.
这是《圣经》中的《启示录》
that's revelations.
当她在画的时候
since when does the book of revelations
有鬼火缠身吗
have jack-o'-lanterns?
额 我们也只了解一点点
it's a,uh,it's a little-known translation.
安娜的父亲是教堂牧师
well,anna's father was a church deacon.
当她病了后
when she became ill,
她的幻想总带有宗教的色彩
her paranoia took on religious overtones.
她深信恶魔
she was convinced the devil
会崛起并终结整个世界
was about to rise up and end the world.
我希望你能找到她
i hope you find her.
她这样单独出去很危险
it's dangerous for her to be out there alone right now.
可能没人
maybe they're not home.
车都停在车道上
both cars in the driveway.
米尔顿夫妇
mr. and mrs. milton?
我们是来自治安部的
we're from the sheriff's department.
我们只是想来问你们几个问题
we just wanted to ask you a couple of questions.
硫磺
sulfur.
恶魔们在这里袭击我们
the demons beat us here.
不管和安娜作的是什么交易
whatever the deal is with this anna girl --
是的  他们想要她  他们不是无目的的
yeah,they want her. they're not screwing around.
好了  那么我是被隔离的女孩
all right,so,i'm "girl,interrupted,"
我知道启示录在讲什么
and i know the score of the apocalypse,
被吓坏了
just busted out of the nut-box...
顺便用一下超能力
possibly using superpowers,by the way.
要我去哪里
where do i go?
你有安娜笔记本里的画
hey,you got those sketches from anna's notebook?
好
yeah.
我们去看看
let me see 'em.
看看这个
check this out.
她画的是教堂的玻璃窗
she was drawing the window of her church.
一遍又一遍
over and over.
如果你是个虔诚徒  被吓坏了
if you were religious,scared,
魔鬼又在缠上你
and had demons on your ass,
你会去哪里
where would you go to feel safe?
迪恩
dean.
安娜
anna?
我们不是来伤害你的  我们是来帮助你的
we're not gonna hurt you. we're here to help.
我叫萨姆  这是我哥哥 迪恩
my name is sam. this is my brother,dean.
萨姆
sam?
是不是萨姆 温彻斯特
not sam winchester?
是的
uh,yeah.
你是迪恩
and you're dean.
那个迪恩
the dean?
我想是的
well,yeah.the dean,i guess.
真的是你
it's really you.
我的上帝啊
oh,my god.
天使们讨论过你
the angels talk about you.
你在地狱的时候
you were in hell,
但卡西迪奥把你救出地狱
but castiel pulled you out,
某些天使认为你可以拯救我们
and some of them think you can help save us.
有些一直不喜欢你
and some of them don't like you at all.
他们最近一直在说你们
they talk about you all the time lately.
我觉得我了解你们
i feel like i know you.
你能和天使说话
so,you talk to angels?
不  不可能
oh,no. no,no way.
他们可能不知道我的存在
um,they probably don't even know i exist.
我只是某些  不小心听到
i just kind of...overhear them.
你偷听到的
you overhear them?
对  有时他们在交谈的时候  我只是
yeah,they talk,and sometimes i just...
在脑子里出现他们谈的内容
hear them in my head.
比如  现在
like...right now?
现在没有  但之前有很多
not right this second,but a lot.
我不能不去听他们的的话  太多了
and i can't shut them out,there are so many of them.
所以他们把你关一群疯子中间
so,they lock you up with a case of the crazies
当你正在
when really you were just...
收挺天使们的话
tuning in to angel radio?
是的
yes.
谢谢
thank you.
安娜  你什么时候开始能听到的
anna,when did the voices start?
还记得么
do you remember?
9月18号  我很确定
i can tell you exactly september 18th.
是我从地狱出来的那天
the day i got out of hell.
我清楚的听到第一个词是
first words i heard,clear as a bell
迪恩 温彻斯特得救了
"dean winchester is saved."
你怎么想
what do you think?
出乎我的意料
it's above my pay grade,man.
至少我们知道恶魔们为什么这样想你死
well,at least now we know why the demons want you so bad.
他们抓到你
they get ahold of you,
就能听到敌对方的所有事
they can hear everything the other side's cooking.
你也是个天使
you're 1-900-angel.
你知道我的父母还好么
hey,um,do you know are my parents okay?
我还没回家
i -- i didn't go home.
我当时很害怕
i was afraid.
你们找到那个女孩了么
you got the girl.
-很好  我们走  -她的脸
good,let's go. oh! her face!
-没关系  他们来帮我们的  -别太肯定
it's okay.she's here to help. yeah,don't be so sure.
-赶紧走  -为什么
we have to hurry. why?
因为高等级恶魔们都赶来了
because a demon's coming --big-timer.
我们可以晚些再和他们交战 迪恩
we can fight later,dean.
很好  简单
well,that's pretty convenient --
我们找到她的时候才出现
showing up right when we find the girl
充当好人
with some bigwig on your tail?
不是我带他来的  是你  什么
i didn't bring him here.you did.what?
他从你们从这女孩家里出来的时候一直跟踪你们
he followed you from the girl's house.
我们该走了 迪恩
we got to go now. dean.
太迟了
it's too late.
他来了
he's here.
呆在这里别动
okay. stay in there.don't move.
-不 萨姆  你必须现在把他抓出来  -等一下
no,sam,you gotto pull him right away.whoa,hold on a sec.
现在不是探究萨姆黑暗力量的时候
now's not the time to bellyache about sam going dark side.
这么做能除去那个恶魔  要么我们死
he does his thing,he exorcises that demon,or we die.
这个手势
that tickles.
你还不够力量和我对抗 萨姆
you don't have the juice to take me on,sam.
你好 迪恩
hello again,dean.
来吧 迪恩
come on,dean.
还没认出我么
don't you recognize me?
我忘记了  那时我是个儿科医生
oh,i forgot i'm wearing a pediatrician.
但我们关系很好
but we were so close...
在地狱里
in hell.
阿拉斯泰尔
alastair.
你该更用点力  孩子
you're gonna have to try a whole lot harder than that,son.
你快搞完了没
are you almost done?
我尽快了
i'm going as fast as i can.
你知道的
good,'cause you know
我的肩膀脱臼了
i got a dislocated shoulder over here.
对
yeah.
我缝完了就把帮你把肩膀弄好
I'll pop it back when I'm finished.
把酒给我
Give me that.
那么说你把那有魔力的刀弄丢了 是吗
So,you lost the magic knife,huh?
是的 为了救你
Yeah,saving your ass.
那恶魔是他妈的谁
Who the hell was that demon?
不是什么好鸟
No one good.
我们该找到安娜
We got to find Anna.
露比找到她了 我想她不会有事的
Ruby's got her I'm sure she's Okay.
好吧
All right.
来吧
Come on.
数三下
On three.
1...
你就那么相信露比
You sure about ruby?
因为我觉得她像是有那么点儿
'cause i think it's just as likely
利用我们去找那个能听天使说话的女孩
she used us to find radio girl
然后再带着那个恶魔来宰了我们
and then brought that demon in to kill us.
不会的 她带走安娜是要保护安娜
No,she took Anna to keep her safe.
是啊
Yeah.
那么 她怎么不打电话告诉我们她在哪
Well,why hasn't she called to tell us where she is?
因为那个恶魔说不定现在正盯着我们呢
Because that demon is probably watching us right now,
等着再一次跟踪我们找到安娜
Waiting to follow us right back to Anna again.
这就是为什么他放我们溜走
That's why he let us go.
你管这叫放我们溜走
You call this letting us go?
是的
Yeah,I do.
想想吧 要杀我们随时可以动手
Look,killing us would've been no problem to that thing.
这就是为什么现在我们要低调
That's why,for now,we just got to lay low
等着露比联系我们
and wait for Ruby to contact us.
她怎么可能那么做
How's she gonna do that?
你怎么就那么相信她
Why do you trust her so much?
我告诉过你
I told you.
你该告诉我更多的事
You got to do better than that.
嘿 我可不是想要和你干仗
Hey,and I'm not trying to pick a fight here.
我是说我真的想理解你
I mean,I really want to understand.
但我需要知道得更多
but I need to know more.
我是说 我应该知道得更多
I mean,I deserve to know more.
因为...
Because...
她救了我的命
She saved my life.
谢谢你对我那么贴心 萨姆
Thanks for keeping this warm for me,Sam.
露比
Ruby.
欢迎归队
It's nice to be back.
我来的地方比地狱更险恶
Where I was,even for hell,it was nasty.
我想我真的把莉莉丝惹毛了
I guess I really pissed lilith off.
想象我是多么宽心当莉莉丝给我最后一次机会
Imagine my relief when she gave me one last chance
把它拨乱反正
to take it topside.
而我全部要做的就是找到你
And all I had to do was find you
宰了你
and kill you.
好吧
Fine.
悉听尊便
Go ahead!
动手吧
Do it.
拿着钥匙 我们该走了
Grab your keys.we got to go.
现在
Now!
你知道什么听起来最棒么
You know what sounds good?
炸薯条
French fries.
我饿死了
I'm starving.
我才爬出地狱 我应该享受一下
I just escaped hell.I deserve a treat.
要知道如果你感谢我我会很开心的
You know,a "thank you" would be nice.
谁叫你过来帮我的
Who asked for your help?
你不明白我所经历过的
You have no idea what I've been through.
当莉莉丝被惹毛了 她就要开始搞你了
When lilith gets pissed,she gets creative.
你想听听
You want to hear
我在地狱里看到的惨相吗
about the corners of hell I've seen,Sam?
不，我不想
No,I don't.
我要做的是让她相信我很抱歉
And the things I had to do to convince her I was sorry?
我是可以相信的
that I could be trusted?
那么 你一定会得到一个超级圣诞大礼包
Well,this'll definitely get you a fat Christmas bonus.
真好笑
Very funny.
我逃出来...就为了你 萨姆
I'm a fugitive...for you,sam.
我历尽艰险回到你身边
I took all of this risk to get back to you,
所以 我应该得到他妈的一声谢谢
So,yeah,I deserve a damn "thank you."
谁叫你过来救我的
Who asked you to save me?
我只是想帮忙
I'm just trying to help.
你能帮我救救迪恩吗
Can you help me save Dean?
不
No.
我不知道有什么人可以强大到救他
Nothing I know of is powerful enough to do that.
而且我对你没有利用价值了
then I have no use for you.
你说什么 滚出去
What? Get out.
萨姆
Sam.
你附在谁身上 露比
Whose body are you riding,Ruby?
该你什么事
What do you care?
你以前从来没问过我
You've never asked me that before.
那我现在问你
I'm asking now.
一个小秘书
Some secretary.
给她自由 萨姆...
Let her go. Sam...
或者我直接把你送回地狱
or i send you right back to hell.
很好，拔出来
all right,pull it.
我该怎样才能搞点薯条来呢
who do i have to kill to get some french fries around here?
试试看
proof.
这哥们真有社会道德意识
this body is 100% socially conscious.
我很环保的
i recycle.
AL GORE会自豪的
al gore would be proud.
你不会想让我穿一只破鞋吧
you didn't want me to take a body with someone in it,
我保证鬼魂已经消失了
and i made sure that the spirit was gone.
房间空空如也 你很开心
apartment was empty.you happy?
你怎么会在这
why are you here?
我无法把迪恩带回来
i can't bring dean back.
但是我能给你一些其他你要的东西
but i can get you something else that you want.
那是什么
...what's that?
莉莉丝
lilith.
你无论如何都要我用我的邪恶力量
you want me to use my psychic whatever.
瞧 我知道这会有点古怪
look,i know that it spooks you --
别说了 走吧
skip the speech.i'm ready.
走
let's go.
老兄 悠着点
slow down there,cowboy.
只管告诉我该做什么
just tell me what i have to do.
历历史就是个胆小的婊子
look,lilith is one scary bitch.
我在地狱时和她聊过
when i was in the pit,there was talk.
她正在搞一个大阴谋
she's cooking up something big --
末日天启
apocalyptic big.
所以我们该宰了她
so let's kill her.
你还想下去再剩半天命回来
you want to go in there and half-ass it like before?
时间多的足够可以解决问题
we have the time to get it right.
那就着手干吧
let's get it right.
说干就干
okay.
你要我干嘛
what do you want from me?
耐心点
well,a little patience...
保持清醒
and sobriety.
答应我
promise me that...
我会教授你我知道的一切
and i will teach you everything i know.
怎样
so?
她教了你什么
what'd she teach you?
我学的第一件事
well,the first thing i learned...
我真是个蹩脚学生
...i'm a crappy student.
一点都不好笑
not funny.
慢慢来 萨姆 会有起色的
just give it time,sam.it'll get better.
什么
what?
难道我需要更多的练习
i need more practice?
我不是指驱魔
i'm not talking about pulling demons.
我理解迪恩的离开对你是
i know losing dean was...
我不想提这事
i don't want to talk about it.
你知道吗
you know what?
你什么时候开始训斥我来了
where do you get off slapping me
用一些像时间会治愈一切的废话来安慰我
with that greeting-card,time-heals crap?
你他妈的知道什么啊
what the hell do you know?
我曾经也是人类
i used to be human.
我知道失去亲人时的痛苦
and i still remember what it feels like to lose someone.
我很抱歉
i'm sorry.
别
don't.
我做不到
i can't.
萨姆 你并不孤单
sam,you're not alone.
你要干吗
what are you doing?
萨姆 都会好起来的
sam,it's okay!
不 我没事 真的
no,that is anything but okay!
怎么了
what's wrong?
what's wrong?!
我从哪上手
where do i start?
是不是因为这躯壳
is it because of the body?
之前我告诉过你
because i told you --
我还是我 外表不一样而已
it's all me inside of here.
还是我
there is no one else.
萨姆 我还在 完好无损
and it's nice inside this body,sam.
如假包换
soft and warm.
你干吗呢
what are you doing?
是吗 可你真是给吓坏了
isn't it 'cause you're really scared
要一个魔鬼一起去
to go there with a demon?
怎么了 是不是有违常理不符合逻辑
because it's wrong and it's bad and we shouldn't?
萨姆
sam?
怎么
yeah?
说的太多了
too much information.
早告诉过你 我完好无缺
hey,i told you i was coming clean.
话是没错 不过我还是不习惯
yeah,but now i feel dirty.
得了 你凑合着看看吧
okay,well,uh,brain-stabbing imagery aside...
目前为止 都符合你所说的
so far,all you've told me about
就一傻走狗 你以为自己谁呢 操
is a manipulative bitch who,uh,screwed you,
对付你还要稍微动动脑子
played mind games with you,
然后根据书里对你百般顺从并最后推倒你
and did everything in the book to get you to go bad.
不错 好戏还在后头
yeah,well,there's more to the story.
请
just...
别这么暴露
skip the nudity,please.
这样好多了
pretty soon after...that,
我组合几个符号
um...i put together some signs...
是一种征兆
omens.
预示着什么
saying what?
莉莉丝来了
lilith was in town.
我想先挫挫她的锐气
and i wanted to strike her first.
你根本就还没有准备好
you're not ready yet.
要不就现在  要不永远都不去
it's now or never.
不  我们可以等到你完全准备好了再去
no,we got to wait until you get it right.
你之前还没有成功过
you haven't been too successful.
行了  我会用这个
all right,i'll use this.
停一下
stop.
你不能像只无头苍蝇一样乱撞  萨姆
you can't just fly in there reckless,sam.
我们是要你杀了那个贱人
we need you to take the bitch out.
哦  我会杀了她的
oh,i'll take her out all right.
你只有一次机会  你就是这一次机会
you get one shot,and you're it.
你是唯一个可以办到这一点的  萨姆
you're the only one who can do it,sam.
所以如果是她把你先杀死了的话
so if she kills you first...
会怎样
what?
你根本就不想活了
you don't want to survive this.
-拜托  -这简直就是神风敢死队的自杀式袭击
-come on. -it's a kamikaze attack.
你就是去送死的
you want to die fighting lilith.
简直是胡扯
that's stupid.
不  那就是事实
no,it's the truth,
因为如果你杀了她而拯救了世界
because if you kill her and you survive this,
你就没有了你哥哥的陪伴不得不孤单的活着
then you have to go on without your brother!
这绝对不是迪恩想要的
this isn't what dean would've wanted.
这绝不是他牺牲了自己想要换来的
this isn't what he died for.
给我让开
get out of my way.
不  萨姆
no,sam.
这是自寻死路
this is suicide!
求求你  我想要回家
please,i want to go home.
莉莉丝要我转达她的歉意
lilith sends her regrets.
她无法守约了
she couldn't make it.
带走那个女孩快跑
take the girl and run!
过来
come on.
露比  你制造了不少麻烦
ruby,you're in so much trouble.
我们会让你  呆在地下室
we're gonna make you...down in the basement.
有点东西我们想要让你尝尝
the things we're gonna do to you.
萨姆
sam.
我很好
i'm okay.
谢谢
thanks.
露比是为了我回来的
ruby came back for me.
无论你怎么说  她曾经救过我
whatever you have to say,she saved me.
更重要的是  她了解我
more than that,she got through to me.
她对我说的事
what she said to me...
你从来都不会对我说
it's what you would've said.
如果不是为了她  我根本就不可能会在这儿
if it wasn't for her,i wouldn't be here.
客房服务
housekeeping.
现在不需要
not now!
先生  我至少得换上干净的毛巾
sir,i've got clean towels.
难道你不能把它们放在门上吗
couldn't you just leave 'em at the door?
这是我的地址
i'm at this address.
对不起  怎么回事儿
i'm sorry. what?
现在就走
go now.
从厕所窗户走
go through the bathroom window,
别拿车  直接走  别停
don't stop,don't take your car,don't pass go.
停车场和高速公路上都有恶魔
there are demons in the hallway and in the parking lot.
露比
ruby?
对  我只占用这个服务生1分钟
okay,yes,so i'm possessing this maid for a hot minute.
去告我
sue me.
那这个女人怎么办
what about coma girl?
让她慢慢腐烂  回小木屋找安娜
slowly rotting on the floor back at the cabin with anna,
我要快点
so i've got to hurry back.
那里再见
see you when you get there.
走人
go!
-很高兴你能做到  -谢谢
glad you could make it.yeah,thanks.
安娜  你没事吧
anna,are you okay?
我没事
yeah. i think so.
露比和其他恶魔不一样
ruby's not like other demons.
她救了我
she saved my life.
是的  我听说了
yeah,i hear she does that.
我认为我
i guess i...
你知道的
...you know.
什么
what?
我欠你个   为了萨姆
i guess i owe you for...sam.
我只是想  你知道么
and just i want to  you know?
别太为难你自己
don't strain yourself.
好的  我们两清了
okay,then.is the moment over?
好的  因为这个很尴尬
good,'cause that was awkward.
萨姆  我打个电话可以么
hey,sam,you think it'd be safe to make a quick call,
只是告诉我父母我没事
just to tell my parents i'm okay?
他们肯定要抓狂了
they must be completely freaked.
怎么了
what?
安娜
anna,um...
你父母
your parents...
他们怎么了
what about them?
很抱歉
look,i'm sorry.
不可能  他们不会
no,they're not...
安娜 很抱歉
anna,i'm sorry.
为什么要这么对我
why is this happening to me?!
我不知道
i don't know.
他们来了
they're coming.
回到那个房间去
back room!
我的刀呢
where's the knife?
那个
uh...about that...
-你开玩笑吧  -别问我
you're kidding.hey,don't look at me.
谢谢
thanks a lot.
很好  你们正会找时间
great. just peachy.impeccable timing,guys,really.
告诉我他们是来帮忙的
please tell me you're here to help.
我们整天被恶魔追杀
we've been having demon issues all day.
我知道
well,i can see that.
你能解释为什么她会在这里
you want to explain why you have that stain in the room?
为了安娜
we're here for anna.
为了保护她
here for her like...here for her?
别废话
stop talking.
把她交给我们
give her to us.
你们能帮助她么
are you gonna help her?
不是
no.
她必须死
she has to die.